Shayla Quinn

8975 McArthur Avenue, Apt 7C, Miami, FL 35000 shayla.quinn@jeemaiLnet (234)567-8901

Enthusiastic entry-level financial analyst with two years of experience focused on using data to help businesses increase profits. Reduced waste and expenses for financial services companies and created dashboards for senior management and executive staff. Used MS Access and Excel to improve portfolios by at least 5.5% per year.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Finance

University Of Florida, Gainesville, FL August 2015 - December 2018

Key Skills

- « Research to establish facts and draw conclusions
- Examine structures and systems with the help of SQL and other software
- Excellent presentation skills

Certifications

- ACCA Certificate in Data Analytics (CertDA), July 2017
- Microsoft Certified Data Analyst Associate, January 2019

Professional Experience

Financial Analyst I

Enterprise Financial Headquarters, Miami, FL | January 2019 - Present

- Provide bi-weekly and monthly summary reports for North Florida and south Georgia offices and custom dashboards for executive staff
- Found and eliminated recurring errors and duplications, saving the company 2.7% in annual expenses in North Florida and 1.3% in South Georgia offices
- Built data visualization reports showing ways to increase monthly client spend while expanding profit margins by at least 5%

Junior Finance Specialist

Enterprise Financial Services, Gainesville, FL | May 2017-December 2017

- Used SQL to pull important business intelligence data for executive presentation.
- Analyzed customer data to improve upsell and cross-selling opportunities by 10%
- Created a template that decreased data redundancy by at least 12%